I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have kept you talking about all that.
أنا آسف جداً. ما كان عليّ أن أبقيك تتحدث عن كل ذلك.
Please come again.
تفضل بزيارتنا مرة أخرى.
Come again!
تفضل بزيارتنا مرة أخرى!
Okay.
تمام.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
What do you mean the banner's gone?
ماذا تقصد باختفاء اللافتة؟
You think someone reported it and had it removed?
هل تعتقد أن أحدهم أبلغ عنه وتمت إزالته؟
Right.
يمين.
You don't think it was those jerks who did this to Suk Hee, do you?
ألا تعتقد أن هؤلاء الأوغاد هم من فعلوا هذا بسوك هي؟
You can see yourself out. The door's open.
يمكنك الخروج بنفسك. الباب مفتوح.
It's got to be them.
لا بد أنهم هم.
I'm not going to let them get away with this.
لن أدعهم يفلتون بفعلتهم هذه.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
(أطباق سوك هي الجانبية)
What? "Not going to let them get away with this?"
ماذا؟ "لن أدعهم يفلتون بفعلتهم هذه؟"
As if you could do anything about it.
وكأنك تستطيع فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما؟
Go to the office. Now. There's something we need to take care of.
اذهب إلى المكتب. الآن. هناك أمرٌ يجب أن نهتم به.
- What on earth... - I said, go!
- يا إلهي... - قلتُ، اذهب!
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
(أطباق سوك هي الجانبية)
- I'm back. - Jang Mi.
- لقد عدت. - جانغ مي.
They must have something to hide. That's why they took the banner down.
لا بد أن لديهم شيئاً يخفونه. لهذا السبب قاموا بإزالة اللافتة.
Dad?
أب؟
- Jang Mi. Good, you're home. - Why? What's going on?
- جانغ مي: جيد، لقد عدتِ إلى المنزل. - لماذا؟ ما الذي يحدث؟
- Our banner has been removed. - What?
- تمت إزالة شعارنا. - ماذا؟
What do you mean? How could it have been taken down so soon?
ماذا تقصد؟ كيف أمكن إزالته بهذه السرعة؟
You know that lady who sells corn from her truck in that neighborhood?
هل تعرف تلك السيدة التي تبيع الذرة من شاحنتها في ذلك الحي؟
Yes, I know who you mean. She works over in Taean.
نعم، أعرف من تقصد. إنها تعمل في تايان.
I asked her for a favor.
طلبت منها معروفاً.
I asked her to keep an eye on the banner when she drives by.
طلبت منها أن تراقب اللافتة عندما تمر بسيارتها.
But apparently, some public officials showed up today,
لكن يبدو أن بعض المسؤولين الحكوميين حضروا اليوم.
said a complaint had been filed, and took it down.
قال إنه تم تقديم شكوى، وقام بإزالتها.
A complaint?
شكوى؟
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Some people have too much free time. Who reports something like that?
بعض الناس لديهم وقت فراغ أكثر من اللازم. من يبلغ عن شيء كهذا؟
I know, right?
أنا أوافق؟
This has to be the work of the people who did this to Suk Hee...
لا بد أن هذا من فعل الأشخاص الذين فعلوا هذا بسوك هي...
That will be 18 dollars.
سيكون ذلك 18 دولارًا.
Yes, here you are.
نعم، ها أنت ذا.
- Thanks. - I'm sorry.
- شكراً. - أنا آسف.
(The banner has been removed.)
(تمت إزالة اللافتة.)
The banner has been removed.
تمت إزالة اللافتة.
Looks like you reported an illegal banner.
يبدو أنك أبلغت عن لافتة غير قانونية.
It was blocking a traffic light and was a hazard.
كانت تعيق إشارة المرور وتشكل خطراً.
So...
لذا...
That's weird.
هذا غريب.
That customer from earlier also said she reported an illegal banner...
وقالت تلك الزبونة التي تحدثت معها سابقاً إنها أبلغت أيضاً عن لافتة غير قانونية...
Why are so many people filing complaints?
لماذا يقدم الكثير من الناس شكاوى؟
Who did?
من فعل ذلك؟
Oh, that customer who was just here.
أوه، ذلك الزبون الذي كان هنا للتو.
She said she reported an illegal banner because it was a driving hazard.
وقالت إنها أبلغت عن لافتة غير قانونية لأنها كانت تشكل خطراً على القيادة.
I can't tell you how disheartening that was to hear.
لا أستطيع أن أصف لك مدى الإحباط الذي شعرت به عند سماع ذلك.
Ours isn’t located anywhere that would obstruct driving.
موقعنا ليس في أي مكان يعيق القيادة.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
We desperately put up that banner, and they can't even look the other way?
لقد وضعنا تلك اللافتة بيأس، وهم لا يستطيعون حتى أن ينظروا في الاتجاه الآخر؟
I almost told that customer off, but I bit my tongue.
كادت أن أوبخ ذلك الزبون، لكنني كظمت غيظي.
Good thing you did.
أحسنت صنعاً.
People like her will never understand how desperate we are.
أمثالها لن يفهموا أبداً مدى يأسنا.
Anyway, don't you think the person who reported our banner is suspicious?
على أي حال، ألا تعتقد أن الشخص الذي أبلغ عن إعلاننا مثير للريبة؟
I'm sure the person who filed the complaint...
أنا متأكد من أن الشخص الذي قدم الشكوى...
is connected to Suk Hee's accident.
يرتبط ذلك بحادث سوك هي.
You're right. I think so too.
أنت محق. أعتقد ذلك أيضاً.
What's taking him so long?
ما الذي يؤخره كل هذا الوقت؟
So? How did it go?
إذن؟ كيف سارت الأمور؟
Yes, it's been handled.
نعم، لقد تم التعامل مع الأمر.
You made sure they can't find out who filed the complaint, right?
لقد تأكدت من أنهم لا يستطيعون معرفة من قدم الشكوى، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, don't worry.
نعم، لا تقلق.
Good. Let those pathetic fools hang their banners.
حسنًا. دع هؤلاء الحمقى البائسين يعلقون راياتهم.
A lot of good it will do them.
سيعود ذلك عليهم بالكثير من الخير.
Knock, knock.
طرق طرق.
Chef Kang?
الزعيم كانغ؟
How about some tea?
ما رأيك ببعض الشاي؟
Don't be so stuffy. It's our break time.
لا تكن متزمتاً للغاية. إنه وقت استراحتنا.
There's no reason we can't have a cup of tea, is there?
لا يوجد سبب يمنعنا من تناول كوب من الشاي، أليس كذلك؟
Unlike some people, I'm not idle.
على عكس بعض الناس، أنا لست عاطلاً عن العمل.
Playing hard to get is only attractive in moderation.
التظاهر بالصعوبة في الوصول إليه لا يكون جذاباً إلا باعتدال.
And I'm not a very patient person.
وأنا لست شخصاً صبوراً جداً.
Your patience won't be required.
لن تحتاج إلى الصبر.
You're a distraction. Please leave.
أنت مصدر إلهاء. من فضلك ارحل.
Jun Ho!
جون هو!
Oh my goodness. Director Ma, I didn't realize you were here.
يا إلهي! يا مخرجة، لم أكن أعلم أنكِ هنا.
You're on a first-name basis with Chef Kang?
هل أنت على علاقة ودية مع الشيف كانغ؟
Well...
حسنًا...
We've just been close ever since we were in school together.
لقد كنا مقربين منذ أن كنا في المدرسة معًا.
- What are you doing here? - I'm here to work, of course,
- ماذا تفعل هنا؟ - أنا هنا للعمل، بالطبع.
unlike some people.
على عكس بعض الناس.
- Here are the junior chef résumés. - Okay.
- هذه هي السير الذاتية للطهاة المبتدئين. - حسناً.
I'll review these, Assistant Manager Jin.
سأراجع هذه يا مساعد المدير جين.
Director Ma, are you just going to keep standing there?
يا مخرج ما، هل ستظل واقفاً هناك؟
Getting in my way?
هل تعترض طريقي؟
Just pretend I'm your shadow. Then I won't be in your way, will I?
تخيل أنني ظلك. حينها لن أكون عائقاً في طريقك، أليس كذلك؟
You're sure CEO Chae isn't here, right?
أنت متأكد من أن الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي ليس هنا، أليس كذلك؟
I'm telling you, she's not.
أقول لك، إنها ليست كذلك.
The CEO should be at the office now. Why would she be here?
كان من المفترض أن تكون الرئيسة التنفيذية في المكتب الآن. لماذا ستكون هنا؟
She's the CEO. She does whatever she wants.
هي الرئيسة التنفيذية. تفعل ما يحلو لها.
So, what? You're saying you don't believe me?
إذن، ماذا؟ هل تقول إنك لا تصدقني؟
No, it's fine. As long as Hwa Young isn't here.
لا، لا بأس. طالما أن هوا يونغ ليست هنا.
Chairman! I'm here!
سيدي الرئيس! أنا هنا!
Darn it.
يا إلهي.
CEO Chae, Yeom San Wol just came home and is meeting with the Chairman.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، يوم سان وول، عاد لتوه إلى المنزل وهو يجتمع مع رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
Yeom San Wol.
يوم سان وول.
So you're ignoring my warning and picking a fight with me, is that it?
إذن أنت تتجاهل تحذيري وتفتعل مشكلة معي، أليس كذلك؟
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
(الرئيسة التنفيذية تشاي هوا يونغ)
Don't you dare treat Mrs. Yeom so disrespectfully.
إياك أن تعامل السيدة يوم بهذه الطريقة غير المحترمة.
If you keep treating Mrs. Yeom like that, I won't let it slide.
إذا استمررت في معاملة السيدة يوم بهذه الطريقة، فلن أتجاهل الأمر.
Why aren't you saying anything?
لماذا لا تقول شيئاً؟
Father.
أب.
She's a friend of mine.
إنها صديقتي.
- How could you and my friend... - Enough.
- كيف يمكنك أنت وصديقي... - كفى.
How dare you meddle in your father-in-law's affairs?
كيف تجرؤ على التدخل في شؤون والد زوجتك؟
Fine, Yeom San Wol.
حسناً، يوم سان وول.
I'll show you exactly who you're messing with.
سأريك بالضبط مع من تعبث.
Take personnel action against Jin Hong Ju, Yeom San Wol's daughter, immediately.
اتخاذ إجراءات تأديبية فورية ضد جين هونغ جو، ابنة يوم سان وول.
Yes, ma'am.
نعم يا سيدتي.
She should know by now that the more she acts up,
كان ينبغي عليها أن تعلم الآن أنه كلما زاد تصرفها السيئ،
the worse it will be for her daughter.
سيكون الأمر أسوأ بالنسبة لابنتها.
If she's a fool, she should know her place.
إذا كانت حمقاء، فعليها أن تعرف حدودها.
Who does she think she is, challenging me?
من تظن نفسها حتى تتحدىني؟
That feels so good.
هذا شعور رائع.
See? This is why I wish I could come every day...
أرأيت؟ لهذا السبب أتمنى لو أستطيع المجيء كل يوم...
and give you a nice massage, Chairman.
وسأقدم لك تدليكاً لطيفاً، أيها الرئيس.
But I'm too afraid of CEO Chae to even come here.
لكنني أخشى الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي لدرجة أنني لا أستطيع حتى المجيء إلى هنا.
Don't worry. I gave her a piece of my mind,
لا تقلقي. لقد وبختها بشدة.
so CEO Chae won't be able to say a thing to you.
لذا لن يتمكن الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي من قول أي شيء لك.
- Really? - Of course. You can bet on it.
- حقاً؟ - بالطبع. يمكنك المراهنة على ذلك.
Who would dare disobey me?
من يجرؤ على عصياني؟
Chairman.
رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
You're the only one who ever looks out for me.
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي يهتم لأمري.
Thank you for saying that.
شكراً لك على قول ذلك.
Jang Mi.
جانغ مي.
Don't overdo it with your injured hand. I'll do it.
لا تجهد يدك المصابة كثيراً. سأفعل ذلك أنا.
It's fine, Dad. It's all healed. I'm wearing a glove to keep it dry.
لا بأس يا أبي، لقد شُفي تماماً. أرتدي قفازاً لأحافظ عليه جافاً.
I swear, whoever did this to my little princess's hand...
أقسم بالله، من فعل هذا بيد أميرتي الصغيرة...
is going to get it from me.
سوف يحصل عليه مني.
Dad, do you really think I would've just let it go?
يا أبي، هل تعتقد حقاً أنني كنت سأتجاهل الأمر؟
I already taught them a lesson.
لقد لقنتهم درساً بالفعل.
I get my temper from you, you know.
أتعلم أنني ورثت غضبي منك.
What?
ماذا؟
That's my girl.
هذه هي فتاتي.
"Let's Have a Drink" is a dance-trot song.
"Let's Have a Drink" هي أغنية رقص من نوع التروت.
Dance-trot. Not that old-fashioned cheesy stuff.
رقصة التروت. ليس ذلك النوع القديم المبتذل.
You have to go full-throttle the whole time. Got it?
عليك أن تضغط على دواسة الوقود بالكامل طوال الوقت. هل فهمت؟
- Right. - Listen.
- صحيح. - استمع.
Let's have a drink
لنشرب شيئاً
Let's go all night long
لنسهر طوال الليل، لنشرب شيئاً.
Tonight, right here,
الليلة، هنا تحديداً،
Make the "o" sound a little nasally.
اجعل صوت حرف "o" أنفيًا بعض الشيء.
It has to be cutesy like this.
يجب أن يكون الأمر لطيفاً كهذا.
Oh.
أوه.
Just copy him, Tae Pyung.
قلّده يا تاي بيونغ.
It's okay. Just relax and follow his lead.
لا بأس. فقط استرخِ واتبع توجيهاته.
You must nail the audition today, right?
يجب أن تتألق في اختبار الأداء اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
Let's have a drink
لنشرب شيئاً
Let's go all night long
لنسهر طوال الليل، لنشرب شيئاً.
Tonight, you and I
الليلة، أنا وأنت
Hold on!
يتمسك!
Hey, stop with the cheesy old-school vibe.
يا رجل، توقف عن هذه الأجواء القديمة المبتذلة.
I'm sorry, sir. He's not normally like this.
أنا آسف يا سيدي. إنه ليس على هذا الحال عادةً.
I'm sorry to ask, sir, could you please show me again?
أعتذر عن السؤال يا سيدي، هل يمكنك أن تريني إياه مرة أخرى؟
All right, last time. Listen up. You know I was in Special Forces, right?
حسنًا، هذه المرة الأخيرة. استمعوا جيدًا. أنتم تعلمون أنني كنت في القوات الخاصة، أليس كذلك؟
- Yes, sir. - Focus!
- نعم سيدي. - ركّز!
Focus!
ركز!
Here I go.
ها أنا ذا ذاهب.
Let's have a drink
لنشرب شيئاً
Let's go all night long
لنسهر طوال الليل، لنشرب شيئاً.
Do the money spin
قم بتدوير النقود
And another one
وآخر
- And keep drinking - Excuse me, sir.
- واستمر في الشرب - عفواً سيدي.
Are you laughing?
هل تضحك؟
- No. - Are you messing with me?
- لا. - هل تمزح معي؟
- No, sir! - Sit! Stand! About-face! Hit the deck!
- لا يا سيدي! - اجلس! قف! استدر! انبطح أرضاً!
Hey, wait a second. Hey! What's your father do?
مهلاً، انتظر لحظة. مهلاً! ما هي وظيفة والدك؟
My father runs a side dish shop.
والدي يدير محلًا لبيع الأطباق الجانبية.
Let's have a drink
لنشرب شيئاً
Let's go all night long
لنسهر طوال الليل، لنشرب شيئاً.
Tonight, you and I
الليلة، أنا وأنت
We'll become one and keep drinking
سنصبح واحداً ونستمر في الشرب
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
I'll find you another place to sing. For now, just go and wait.
سأجد لك مكاناً آخر لتغني فيه. أما الآن، فاذهب وانتظر.
I have other songs.
لدي أغاني أخرى.
- Please give me one more chance... - Quiet.
- أرجوك امنحني فرصة أخرى... - اصمت.
What's your plan?
ما هي خطتك؟
Why would you go to the trouble of having Oh Tae Pyung sing?
لماذا تتكبد عناء جعل أوه تاي بيونغ يغني؟
A song that doesn't suit him in the slightest, no less.
أغنية لا تناسبه على الإطلاق، لا أقل من ذلك.
Kang Hyuk, contact the head of the agency.
كانغ هيوك، اتصل برئيس الوكالة.
Get Oh Tae Pyung a gig on some small stage out in the boonies.
ساعدوا أوه تاي بيونغ في الحصول على فرصة للعزف على مسرح صغير في منطقة نائية.
That's not difficult, though.
لكن هذا ليس بالأمر الصعب.
I don't understand why you want to get Oh Tae Pyung a gig...
لا أفهم لماذا تريد أن تحصل على وظيفة لأوه تاي بيونغ...
You've been by my side for so long, and you still can't figure me out?
لقد كنت بجانبي لفترة طويلة، وما زلت لا تستطيع فهمي؟
Jung Suk Hee may have the mind of a child, but she's still alive, right?
قد يكون لدى جونغ سوك هي عقل طفلة، لكنها لا تزال على قيد الحياة، أليس كذلك؟
And since she's alive, who knows what variables might arise?
وبما أنها على قيد الحياة، فمن يدري ما هي المتغيرات التي قد تنشأ؟
Whether she'll remain an amnesiac half-wit...
هل ستبقى فاقدة للذاكرة وشبه غبية...
or get struck by lightning and snap out of it, nobody knows.
أو أن تصعقها صاعقة وتفيق من غيبوبتها، لا أحد يعلم.
I see.
أرى.
So you want to use Oh Tae Pyung to keep an eye on her.
إذن أنت تريد استخدام أوه تاي بيونغ لمراقبتها.
Shouldn't we create a way to maintain contact with them?
ألا ينبغي لنا إيجاد طريقة للحفاظ على التواصل معهم؟
That way, if the worst should happen, we'll be able to handle it.
وبهذه الطريقة، إذا حدث الأسوأ، سنكون قادرين على التعامل معه.
Chin up, Oh Tae Pyung.
ارفع رأسك يا أوه تاي بيونغ.
Thanks. Tomorrow is another day.
شكراً. غداً يوم جديد.
That's the spirit.
هذا هو المطلوب.
You know, it's really strange.
أتعلم، إنه أمر غريب حقاً.
Being at that hotel jogged my memory.
وجودي في ذلك الفندق أعاد إليّ ذكرياتي.
About what?
عن ما؟
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Could she be a doppelganger?
هل يمكن أن تكون شبيهة؟
I'm Ma Seo Rin. I'm the Director of Food and Beverage.
أنا ما سيو رين. أنا مدير قسم الأطعمة والمشروبات.
And when did you have time to change your clothes?
ومتى كان لديك الوقت لتغيير ملابسك؟
You weren't wearing your glasses earlier.
لم تكن ترتدي نظارتك في وقت سابق.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Get out of my way. I'm trying to work.
ابتعد عن طريقي. أحاول العمل.
There are probably a lot of look-alikes in the world, right?
ربما يوجد الكثير من الأشخاص الذين يشبهون بعضهم البعض في العالم، أليس كذلك؟
Where did that come from?
من أين أتى ذلك؟
It's just something.
إنه مجرد شيء ما.
It's just that this one rude girl keeps popping up.
الأمر ببساطة أن هذه الفتاة الوقحة تستمر في الظهور.
By the way, take good care of that thing my sister asked you about, okay?
بالمناسبة، اعتني جيداً بذلك الشيء الذي سألتك عنه أختي، حسناً؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Thanks for everything.
شكراً على كل شيء.
I know you're busy with your law practice, but you're helping me, and my sister too.
أعلم أنك مشغول بممارسة مهنة المحاماة، لكنك تساعدني أنا وأختي أيضاً.
Is "thank you" all I'm getting?
هل كلمة "شكراً" هي كل ما سأحصل عليه؟
You've never invited me to your place.
لم تدعني قط إلى منزلك.
- Are you hiding a stash of gold in there? - Alright, I understand.
- هل تخبئ مخبأً من الذهب هناك؟ - حسناً، فهمت.
I'll invite you over and treat you to a proper feast.
سأدعوك إلى منزلي وأقدم لك وليمة شهية.
- Sounds good! I get to see your sister. - You little...
- يبدو جيداً! سأرى أختك. - يا لك من...
- So you had an ulterior motive. - Hey, killing two birds with one stone.
- إذن كان لديك دافع خفي. - حسناً، ضرب عصفورين بحجر واحد.
- Really? - Yes, so when should I have him over?
- حقاً؟ - نعم، متى يجب أن أدعوه إذاً؟
That lawyer friend of yours?
ذلك الصديق المحامي؟
You're saying that lawyer is interested in our Jang Mi?
هل تقول أن هذا المحامي مهتم بجانغ مي خاصتنا؟
Jang Mi's hand hurts. Jang Mi has a boo-boo.
يد جانغ مي تؤلمها. جانغ مي لديها جرح صغير.
He seemed really curious about her.
بدا فضولياً جداً بشأنها.
We've never even met. What's he so curious about?
لم نلتقِ قط. ما الذي يثير فضوله إلى هذا الحد؟
Lawyer Kang is only interested because of me...
المحامي كانغ مهتم بي فقط...
since you're my little sister. Why else would he be interested in you?
بما أنكِ أختي الصغيرة، فلماذا يهتم بكِ لولا ذلك؟
I guess so,
اعتقد ذلك،
but don't you think it might be because we spoke on the phone a few times?
لكن ألا تعتقد أن ذلك قد يكون بسبب أننا تحدثنا عبر الهاتف عدة مرات؟
Right. Jang Mi has a point.
صحيح. كلام جانغ مي منطقي.
Jang Mi has a voice like a songbird. Plus, she's sweet and refined.
جانغ مي تتمتع بصوتٍ عذبٍ كالعصافير المغردة. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، فهي لطيفة وراقية.
Anyone who talks to her on the phone is bound to be charmed by her.
لا بد أن يفتن بها كل من يتحدث معها عبر الهاتف .
But is he handsome?
لكن هل هو وسيم؟
No, wait, what's he like as a person? What matters most is that he's a good man.
لا، انتظر، كيف هو كشخص؟ الأهم هو أنه رجل صالح.
He has to be kind.
عليه أن يكون لطيفاً.
Come on, Dad. Are you trying to find me a husband or something?
هيا يا أبي، هل تحاول أن تجد لي زوجاً أم ماذا؟
Come on. You're all getting way ahead of yourselves.
هيا، أنتم جميعاً تستبقون الأمور كثيراً .
Dad, he's a lawyer. Are we even in his league?
أبي، إنه محامٍ. هل نحن حتى في مستواه؟
Jang Mi, don't you get your hopes up, either.
جانغ مي، لا ترفعي سقف توقعاتك أيضاً.
You're the one getting ahead of yourself. Who said I was getting my hopes up?
أنت من يستبق الأحداث. من قال إنني أرفع سقف توقعاتي؟
When did you say you were inviting the lawyer over?
متى قلت إنك ستدعو المحامي؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Mom, is Dad still not home?
أمي، هل أبي لم يعد إلى المنزل بعد؟
I know. For some reason, your dad has been late every day.
أعلم. لسبب ما، يتأخر والدك كل يوم.
Is he having an affair or something?
هل هو على علاقة غرامية أم ماذا؟
Kang Baek Ho.
أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفاً.
Your father would be the last man in Korea to have an affair.
والدك سيكون آخر رجل في كوريا يقيم علاقة غرامية.
Come on, Mom. How can you be so sure? Dad is still a man, you know.
هيا يا أمي، كيف يمكنكِ أن تكوني متأكدة إلى هذا الحد؟ أبي ما زال رجلاً، كما تعلمين.
If I don't know your father, who does?
إذا كنت لا أعرف والدك، فمن يعرفه؟
With that germaphobia of his...
بسبب هوسه بالنظافة...
He's too timid to ever cheat.
إنه خجول للغاية لدرجة أنه لا يستطيع الغش أبداً.
And besides,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك،
why on earth would your father ever betray me?
لماذا قد يخونني والدك ؟
Your dad only has eyes for me.
والدك لا يرى سواي.
Okay. I know how much Dad loves you.
حسناً. أعرف كم يحبك أبي.
Thank you...
شكرًا لك...
for letting me cry.
لأنك سمحت لي بالبكاء.
I've always seen you as a glamorous and untouchable icon.
لطالما رأيتك كرمز ساحر لا يُمس.
And now...
والآن...
you're my icon.
أنت قدوتي.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
Because you understood how I feel.
لأنك فهمت ما أشعر به.
Surely Father...
بالتأكيد يا أبي...
wouldn't bring Yeom San Wol home, would he?
لن يعيد يوم سان وول إلى المنزل، أليس كذلك؟
No, that's absolutely out of the question.
لا، هذا أمر مستبعد تماماً.
Mom, aren't you going to eat?
أمي، ألن تأكلي؟
Father.
أب.
What if we expedited the process of making Seo Rin the successor?
ماذا لو قمنا بتسريع عملية تعيين سيو رين خليفةً؟
I thought you said I couldn't until I showed some results.
ظننت أنك قلت إنني لا أستطيع حتى أظهر بعض النتائج.
If you take Seo Rin to meet the directors...
إذا اصطحبت سيو رين لمقابلة المخرجين...
and help her make an impression, it'll be a much faster process.
ومساعدتها على ترك انطباع جيد سيجعل العملية أسرع بكثير.
- It clearly shows you approve of Seo Rin. - I'm in.
- هذا يدل بوضوح على موافقتك على سيو رين. - أنا موافق.
At least it's not boring with you, Grandpa.
على الأقل الأمر ليس مملاً معك يا جدي.
You little rascal, do you just come to work to see me?
أيها الوغد الصغير، هل تأتي إلى العمل فقط لرؤيتي؟
It's no fun. Everyone is so incompetent.
الأمر ليس ممتعاً. الجميع غير أكفاء.
Incompetent? What do you mean?
غير كفؤ؟ ماذا تقصد؟
They should just get to the point, but they always beat around the bush.
كان ينبغي عليهم أن يدخلوا في صلب الموضوع مباشرة، لكنهم دائماً ما يلفون ويدورون.
It's so frustrating I could scream.
إنه أمر محبط للغاية لدرجة أنني أكاد أصرخ.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Yes, miss?
نعم يا آنسة؟
Where are the eyeballs? Where did the eyeballs go?
أين العيون؟ أين ذهبت العيون؟
They removed the eyeballs at the market for me.
قاموا بإزالة مقل العيون من أجلي في السوق.
I've lost my appetite.
لقد فقدت شهيتي.
- Without eyeballs, I don't want to eat. - Goodness, you like the eyeballs so much?
- بدون مقل العيون، لا أريد أن آكل. - يا إلهي، هل تحب مقل العيون إلى هذا الحد؟
This won't do.
هذا لن ينفع.
Go to the fish market and gather up every eyeball you can find,
اذهب إلى سوق السمك واجمع كل مقلة عين يمكنك العثور عليها.
and make some porridge for her.
وأعد لها بعض العصيدة.
Would there be a place that only sells fish eyeballs?
هل يوجد مكان يبيع عيون السمك فقط؟
Yes, sir. I'll look into it.
نعم سيدي، سأبحث في الأمر.
Assistant Manager Jin Hong Ju's transfer notice has been posted.
تم نشر إشعار انتقال مساعد المدير جين هونغ جو .
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Did the Chairman really give CEO Chae a piece of his mind?
هل قام رئيس مجلس الإدارة فعلاً بتوبيخ الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي بشدة؟
He sure did.
بالتأكيد فعل ذلك.
So what if Hwa Young tried to warn me?
وماذا لو حاولت هوا يونغ تحذيري؟
The Chairman ignored her...
تجاهلها الرئيس...
and told me to come home. What can she do?
وقالت لي أن أعود إلى المنزل. ماذا يمكنها أن تفعل؟
She'll just have to suck it up.
سيتعين عليها أن تتحمل الأمر.
So, Mom, stop cowering every time CEO Chae says something to you,
إذن يا أمي، توقفي عن الخوف في كل مرة يقول لكِ الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي شيئاً ما.
you need to tighten the reins on her.
عليك أن تشدد قبضتك عليها.
All right, I get it. I have nothing to lose now.
حسناً، فهمت. ليس لدي ما أخسره الآن.
Here, have some of this.
تفضل، خذ بعضاً من هذا.
And make sure to put in a good word for me with the Chairman.
وتأكد من أن تتوسط لي لدى رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
I'm doing all the real work at the hotel. Why am I still just an assistant manager?
أنا أقوم بكل العمل الحقيقي في الفندق. لماذا ما زلت مجرد مساعد مدير؟
(Effective October 6, 2025, Assistant Manager Jin Hong Ju...)
(اعتبارًا من 6 أكتوبر 2025، مساعد المدير جين هونغ جو...)
(transferred to the branch in New Delhi, India)
(تم نقلها إلى الفرع في نيودلهي، الهند)
This is ridiculous.
هذا أمر سخيف.
Mom.
أم.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Oh my godness. What is this outrageous nonsense?
يا إلهي! ما هذا الهراء الفاحش؟
They're sending you to India, of all places.
إنهم يرسلونك إلى الهند، من بين جميع الأماكن.
Has Hwa Young lost her mind? Is she insane?
هل فقدت هوا يونغ عقلها؟ هل هي مجنونة؟
Does she really think I'll just go quietly?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنني سأرحل بهدوء؟
I'm not going. No way.
لن أذهب. مستحيل.
It looks like Hwa Young still doesn't get the picture,
يبدو أن هوا يونغ لا تزال غير مدركة للأمر،
she's completely clueless about how much the Chairman favors me.
إنها جاهلة تماماً بمدى تفضيل رئيس مجلس الإدارة لي.
That's why she'd pull a disloyal stunt like this.
ولهذا السبب قد تقوم بمثل هذه الحيلة الخائنة.
I'm going to teach her a lesson.
سألقنها درساً.
Have some tea, Assistant Manager Jin.
تفضل بشرب بعض الشاي يا مساعد المدير جين.
It's a Darjeeling I've been saving for a special occasion.
إنه نبيذ دارجيلنغ كنت أدخره لمناسبة خاصة.
It's from India.
إنها من الهند.
I cannot accept this, ma'am.
لا أستطيع قبول هذا يا سيدتي.
Why India all of a sudden?
لماذا الهند فجأة؟
- What am I supposed to do in India? - What do you mean?
- ماذا يفترض بي أن أفعل في الهند؟ - ماذا تقصد؟
You know how huge India's population is, don't you?
أنت تعلم مدى ضخامة عدد سكان الهند، أليس كذلك؟
- Do some market research... - Ma'am.
- أجري بعض أبحاث السوق... - سيدتي.
That's rich, Assistant Manager Jin.
هذا كلامٌ طريف يا مساعد المدير جين.
You were thrilled about the US training. So what's wrong with India?
كنتَ متحمساً جداً للتدريب في الولايات المتحدة. فما المشكلة في الهند؟
Why are you making such a fuss about it?
لماذا تُثير كل هذه الضجة حول هذا الموضوع؟
Technically, it was the Chairman who sent me for that training, not you.
من الناحية الفنية، كان رئيس مجلس الإدارة هو من أرسلني لهذا التدريب، وليس أنت.
So you're refusing to go to India?
إذن أنت ترفض الذهاب إلى الهند؟
Ma'am...
سيدتي...
Listen to me carefully.
استمع إليّ جيداً.
I'm transferring you to India...
سأقوم بتحويلك إلى الهند...
so you can go to a larger market, broaden your horizons,
حتى تتمكن من الذهاب إلى سوق أكبر، وتوسيع آفاقك،
and gain more experience. I'm giving you an opportunity.
واكتسب المزيد من الخبرة. أنا أمنحك فرصة.
And the board of directors agrees.
ويوافق مجلس الإدارة على ذلك.
It's a waste to let a talent like you rot away in one place.
من المؤسف أن نترك موهبة مثلك تتلاشى في مكان واحد.
Don't give it a second thought. Just hand over your duties by month's end.
لا تتردد. سلّم مهامك قبل نهاية الشهر.
And get ready to leave for India.
واستعد للمغادرة إلى الهند.
I'll have to think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
Jung Suk Hee.
جونغ سوك هي.
Now, you just need to stay quiet, just like you are now,
الآن، كل ما عليك فعله هو التزام الصمت، كما تفعل الآن.
and remain a half-wit forever.
ويبقى أحمق إلى الأبد.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
You'll approve the banner?
هل ستوافق على اللافتة؟
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Okay.
تمام.
Dad!
أب!
The county office just approved the banner.
وافق مكتب المقاطعة للتو على اللافتة.
That's a relief. That's great news.
هذا مريح. هذا خبر رائع.
Dad, Jang Mi! I finally got a job!
أبي، جانغ مي! لقد حصلت أخيراً على وظيفة!
What? Where?
ماذا؟ أين؟
It's not a prime venue, but I finally get to perform on stage.
ليس مكاناً مميزاً، لكنني أخيراً سأتمكن من الأداء على المسرح.
Really?
حقًا؟
Who on earth hired you?
من الذي وظفك يا ترى؟
I passed an audition.
لقد اجتزت اختبار الأداء.
Dream Hotel's CEO was moved by my singing and set it up for me.
تأثر الرئيس التنفيذي لفندق دريم بغنائي وقام بترتيب الأمر لي.
Tae Pyung said he'd buy a gift for Ok Hee and Tok Hee.
قال تاي بيونغ إنه سيشتري هدية لأوك هي وتوك هي.
Is that for real?
هل هذا حقيقي؟
Just don't get scammed this time. I'm worried you won't really get on stage.
لا تقع ضحية للاحتيال هذه المرة. أخشى ألا تتمكن من الصعود إلى المسرح فعلاً.
- Dad, don't be such a killjoy. - He's right, Dad.
- يا أبي، لا تكن كئيباً هكذا. - هو محق يا أبي.
Tae Pyung, good luck! I'm so happy for you!
تاي بيونغ، حظاً سعيداً! أنا سعيد جداً من أجلك!
But wait, Dream Hotel's CEO was moved by your song?
لكن لحظة، هل تأثر الرئيس التنفيذي لفندق دريم بأغنيتك؟
Am I really supposed to believe that?
هل يُفترض بي حقاً أن أصدق ذلك؟
- Jang Mi, you've become bold. - Anyway, congratulations.
- جانغ مي، لقد أصبحتِ جريئة. - على أي حال، تهانينا.
- You can do it. - I've got this.
- يمكنك فعلها. - أنا قادر على ذلك.
- Rookie. - Yes, Chef.
- مبتدئ. - نعم، أيها الطاهي.
Eat it.
تناوله.
- Excuse me? - I said, eat it.
- عفواً؟ - قلتُ، كُلْه.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
- It's delicious. - Delicious?
- إنه لذيذ. - لذيذ؟
So pasta covered in dish soap tastes good to you?
هل المعكرونة المغطاة بسائل غسل الصحون لذيذة بالنسبة لك؟
You're fired. Get out.
أنت مطرود. اخرج.
I'm sorry, sir. It will never happen again.
أنا آسف يا سيدي. لن يتكرر هذا الأمر أبداً.
A mistake? You don't even have the basics down.
خطأ؟ أنت لا تتقن حتى الأساسيات.
Got it? Now get out!
فهمت؟ الآن اخرج!
Didn't I tell you to get out?
ألم أقل لك أن تخرج؟
What's going on here?
ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
Our customers pay good money to come to this restaurant,
يدفع زبائننا مبالغ جيدة للقدوم إلى هذا المطعم،
so shouldn't we give them their money's worth?
ألا ينبغي لنا أن نمنحهم قيمة أموالهم؟
- Everyone, get back to cooking. - Are you really firing her?
- يا جماعة، عودوا إلى الطبخ. - هل ستطردونها حقاً؟
Didn't you hear me?
ألم تسمعني؟
Won't we be short-handed if you fire her?
ألن نعاني من نقص في الموظفين إذا قمت بفصلها؟
You have to think about the strain it'll put on the other chefs.
عليك أن تفكر في الضغط الذي سيسببه ذلك على الطهاة الآخرين.
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
This is my kitchen.
هذا مطبخي.
So, you want me to mind my own business?
إذن، تريدني أن أهتم بشؤوني الخاصة؟
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
سأضطر إلى أن أطلب منك المغادرة.
I'm here as a customer.
أنا هنا بصفتي زبوناً.
I'm hungry. Is my food coming out any time soon?
أنا جائع. هل سيصل طعامي قريباً؟
Running things like this,
إدارة الأمور بهذه الطريقة،
I'm extremely concerned...
أنا قلق للغاية...
about how you're going to meet my two-month sales target.
حول كيفية تحقيق هدف المبيعات الخاص بي خلال شهرين.
Here, a present for you.
تفضل، هذه هدية لك.
It's got a bit of a story, which is why it's late.
لها قصة ما، ولهذا السبب تأخرت.
This looks expensive!
هذا يبدو باهظ الثمن!
I don't know what the story is, but thanks, Baek Ho.
لا أعرف ما هي القصة، ولكن شكراً لك يا بايك هو.
So, is she your mother?
إذن، هل هي والدتك؟
Right.
يمين.
You've never met my mom before, have you?
لم تقابل أمي من قبل، أليس كذلك؟
That's why I've been hesitant to invite friends over.
ولهذا السبب كنت مترددًا في دعوة الأصدقاء.
Really?
حقًا؟
If my mom hadn't gotten injured, she could've been your senior.
لو لم تُصب والدتي، لكانت هي الطالبة الأكبر منك.
- My senior? - My mom passed part one of the bar exam,
- زميلي الأكبر؟ - والدتي اجتازت الجزء الأول من امتحان نقابة المحامين،
but she was in an accident before she could take the second part.
لكنها تعرضت لحادث قبل أن تتمكن من القيام بالجزء الثاني.
So she's got beauty and brains?
إذن فهي تتمتع بالجمال والذكاء؟
- Hey, your sister must be gorgeous then. - Why you...
- مهلاً، لا بد أن أختك جميلة جداً. - لماذا أنت...
Jang Mi is pretty.
جانغ مي جميلة.
Tae Pyung is nice.
تاي بيونغ شخص لطيف.
Huh? This is the bathhouse for my bunny.
هاه؟ هذا حمام أرنبي.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Mom, this is my guitar.
أمي، هذه غيتاري.
- No, Jang Mi gave this to me. It's mine. - No, Mom.
- لا، جانغ مي أعطتني هذا. إنه لي. - لا يا أمي.
- Mom, wait. - It's mine.
- أمي، انتظري. - إنه لي.
My bunny's bathhouse.
حمام أرنبي.
(CEO Chae Hwa Young)
(الرئيسة التنفيذية تشاي هوا يونغ)
(CEO's Office)
(مكتب الرئيس التنفيذي)
- They've put the banner back up. - What?
- لقد أعادوا تعليق اللافتة. - ماذا؟
And it looks like they got a permit from the district office this time.
ويبدو أنهم حصلوا على تصريح من مكتب المنطقة هذه المرة.
Those low-lives...
هؤلاء الأوغاد...
See? What did I tell you? They're relentless.
أرأيت؟ ألم أقل لك؟ إنهم لا يكلّون.
That's the thing about these low-lives. They just won't give up.
هذا ما يميز هؤلاء الأوغاد. إنهم لا يستسلمون أبداً.
What are your orders? Should I have it taken down?
ما هي أوامرك؟ هل يجب عليّ حذفها؟
Why are you even asking? Tell them to tear it down!
لماذا تسأل أصلاً؟ قل لهم أن يهدموه!
Hello, Ssangkal.
مرحباً، سجانكال.
Tear down that banner without anyone seeing you.
قم بإزالة تلك اللافتة دون أن يراك أحد.
And be careful not to get caught.
واحرص على ألا يتم القبض عليك.
I wonder what Lawyer Kang looks like.
أتساءل كيف يبدو المحامي كانغ.
He's here.
إنه هنا.
- Come on in. - Oh my gosh, what do I do?
- تفضل بالدخول. - يا إلهي، ماذا أفعل؟
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
Hello, it's a pleasure to meet you. My name is Kang Baek Ho...
أهلاً، تشرفت بلقائكم. اسمي كانغ بايك هو...
Welcome.
مرحباً.
What?
ماذا؟
You!
أنت!
(The First Man)
(الرجل الأول)
I'll have them removed by the end of today.
سأقوم بإزالتها بحلول نهاية اليوم.
They just won't quit.
إنهم لا يستسلمون أبداً.
That's why we have to rip them out by the roots.
ولهذا السبب علينا أن نقتلعهم من جذورهم.
Lawyer Kang, we need to talk.
المحامي كانغ، علينا أن نتحدث.
I only kept quiet to save you the embarrassment.
لقد التزمت الصمت فقط لأجنبك الإحراج.
Do you think I'd choose my love over my own daughter?
هل تعتقد أنني سأختار حبي على ابنتي؟
- You're in love with the Chairman? - I love the Chairman!
- هل أنتِ مغرمة بالرئيس؟ - أنا مغرمة بالرئيس!
Enough.
كافٍ.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
(الترجمة مقدمة من KOCOWA.)